One times one is one.
Two times two is four.
Three times three is nine.
Four times four is sixteen.
Five times five...
Yuanyuan...
I forgot.
Jingyuan,
although he is very mean with his words,
is really good to Ayan.
It's as if he knew he was going to leave.
He prepared so many toys for him.
Yeah.
Axuan,
if one day,
I...
What is it?
Nothing.
The story has reached its end.
Jingyuan has left.
Am I going to leave too?
At some point
that even I can't anticipate.
Yuanyuan.
Why are you ignoring me?
What did you call me?
Yuanyuan.
What about me?
You are Yuanyuan too.
Both of you are Yuanyuan.
Ayan has two Yuanyuans.
Axuan.
Yuanyuan.
Why did that Yuanyuan leave?
I thought human partings and reunions were like the wind,
ending in nothing but a long sleep.
But in this bittersweet virtual world,
in this supposedly cold palace,
I feel a sincere and passionate vitality.
At this moment,
it feels like I'm truly looking at the human world.
Ayan.
That Yuanyuan didn't leave.
And I won't leave either.
Lie down, and I'll tell you a story, okay?
Okay.
User Cangyue Xinglan detected.
Character goal 100% completed.
Main quest of the game completed.
About to exit the virtual world.
Please get ready.
Ah Xuan.
Cangyue.
Goodbye, Si Xingxuan.
Congratulations. The project experience is successfully completed.
What kind of partnership should we switch to?
What partnership?
A lifelong one.
Child-stealing dog.
I didn't.
You did.
I really didn't.
Which is sweeter, the grapes or me?